# **ERNEST PANFILOFF**

## Web Developer

I'm a versatile web developer with experience in various CMS and expertise in Front-End development. I excel at quickly learning new technologies, balancing aesthetics and functionality in every project, and collaborating with clients to achieve their goals.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# IT Associate @ Green Valley Wholefoods

Sep 2021 - Mar 2022

- Successfully implemented and launched an online shop utilizing Shopify for a physical retailer, resulting in the acquisition of the first online customers.
- Created and designed various marketing materials, including leaflets and social media graphics, using Canva and Adobe Photoshop to effectively promote the business and increase brand awareness.
- Edited and customized Shopify template's CSS to enhance the user experience and aesthetic appeal.
- Maintained and updated the e-commerce shop on a regular basis, including uploading products, writing compelling product descriptions, implementing various payment options, and more to ensure a seamless customer experience.

Skills: HTML · CSS · Shopify · E-Commerce · Canva · Adobe Photoshop

# Wordpress Developer @ Hands Off Our Yard

Jan 2021 - Mar 2021

- Successfully satisfied client's needs and requirements by designing and building a website for a client using Wordpress and Elementor.
- Worked on a project from start to finish, including conceptualization, design, development, and deployment.
- Gained experience working with clients to understand their needs and deliver a finished product that met their specifications.

**Skills & Tools:** JavaScript · PHP · Elementor · HTML · CSS · Adobe Photoshop · WordPress

#### **EDUCATION**

## Birkbeck, University of London

FDSc Computing/Information Technology/Web Development

2021 — Present

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Python for Everybody Specialization | University of Michigan
- Digital Skills Bootcamp in Software Development | QA
- Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals | Microsoft

# **ORGANIZATIONS**

BCS, The Chartered Institute for IT (Associate Member)

#### CONTACT

- +447305917272
- ernestas.du@gmail.com
- /in/ernestpanfiloff
- github.com/ernestpanfiloff
- ernestas.netlify.app

### **SKILLS**

- → HTMI
- → CSS
- → Javascript
- → Git & Github
- → OOP
- → Web Accessibility
- → React

# **LANGUAGES**

- ➤ English
- > Lithuanian
- > Polish
- Russian